Okay. "Now holding sides of hearth
in position...
...Iower mantelpiece assembly
onto top tabs."
(Leonard:)Look at that, I built a fireplace
with my own two hands.
(Penny:)You're so butch.
(Leonard:)Aw, I got a little paper cut.
(Penny:)Of course you did.
You're hands are softer than veal.
Oh, uh, before I forget, Saturday I'm planning
a Dungeons & Dragons night with the guys.
(Penny:)That's how you're gonna spend
your Saturday night?
- Come on, I hardly get a chance to play.
- You poor thing.
Is having a real girlfriend
who has sex with you...
(Penny:)...getting in the way
of your board games?
A little bit, yeah.
Oh, great, I've always wanted to play
Dungeons & Dragons.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm sorry,
I should've mentioned this earlier.
(Sheldon:)You're not invited.
(Amy:)Why not?
(Sheldon:)Amy, from time to time,
we men need to break free...
(Sheldon:)...from the shackles of civility and get
in touch with our primal, animalistic selves.
(Amy:)By rolling dice and playing make-believe
with little figurines?
(Sheldon:)Like a bunch of savages.
(Penny:)Saturday night?
But I've been working late all week.
(Bernadette:)- That was gonna be our night.
- I have to go, we play as a group.
And if I'm not there,
then everyone will blame you.
They'll be all, "Bernadette ruined
everything. She's the worst."
So you see, heh,
I have to play Dungeons & Dragons.
(Howard:)For the marriage.
(Bernadette:)You're an idiot.
(Howard:)I'm your idiot. Forever.
(Raj:)So listen, I know we talked about
getting a bite to eat in Silver Lake...
(Raj:)...then seeing the Christmas lights
in Griffith Park...
(Raj:)...but Leonard's talking about
a big D and D game at his place.
(Stuart:)Saturday night just went
from crazy to epic.
(Stuart:)Woo-hoo!